
 [
    {
      "question": " Thin or weak",
      "choice1": "wispy ",
      "choice2": "spawn",
      "choice3": "vital",
      "choice4": "triumphant ",
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "the product or offspring of ",
      "choice1": "wispy ",
      "choice2": "spawn",
      "choice3": "vital",
      "choice4": "triumphant ",
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Urgently needed, very important, or absolutely necessary",
     "choice1": "wispy ",
      "choice2": "spawn",
      "choice3": "vital",
      "choice4": "triumphant ",
      "answer": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "Having achieved victory or success",
      "choice1": "wispy ",
      "choice2": "spawn",
      "choice3": "vital",
      "choice4": "triumphant ",
      "answer": 4
    },
    {
      "question": "to demolish or crush completely",
      "choice1": "Pulverize",
      "choice2": "Shriveled",
      "choice3": "Squall",
      "choice4": "Hallucination ",
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Wrinkled or withered often from age",
      "choice1": "Pulverize",
      "choice2": "Shriveled",
      "choice3": "Squall",
      "choice4": "Hallucination ",
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "sudden violent gusts of wind, often with precipitation",
      "choice1": "Pulverize",
      "choice2": "Shriveled",
      "choice3": "Squall",
      "choice4": "Hallucination ",
      "answer": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "something(such as an image, a sound, or a smell) that seems real but does not really exist",
     "choice1": "Pulverize",
      "choice2": "Shriveled",
      "choice3": "Squall",
      "choice4": "Hallucination ",
      "answer": 4
    },
    {
      "question": "A dark shape in front of a light background",
      "choice1": "Silhouette",
      "choice2": "Bellow",
      "choice3": "Disintegrate",
      "choice4": "Summer solstice",
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "to shout in a deep, loud voice",
      "choice1": "Silhouette",
      "choice2": "Bellow",
      "choice3": "Disintegrate",
      "choice4": "Summer solstice",
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "to break apart into many small parts or pieces",
      "choice1": "Silhouette",
      "choice2": "Bellow",
      "choice3": "Disintegrate",
      "choice4": "Summer solstice",
      "answer": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "the day in the year with the most sunlight (around June 21)",
      "choice1": "Silhouette",
      "choice2": "Bellow",
      "choice3": "Disintegrate",
      "choice4": "Summer solstice",
      "answer": 4
    },
    {
      "question": "a card game played with a special deck of 48 cards",
      "choice1": "Pinochle ",
      "choice2": "Pudgy",
      "choice3": "Incinerates",
      "choice4": "Disintegrate",
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "short and a little fat, chubby",
     "choice1": "Pinochle ",
      "choice2": "Pudgy",
      "choice3": "Incinerates",
      "choice4": "Disintegrate",
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "to destroy by burning",
     "choice1": "Pinochle ",
      "choice2": "Pudgy",
      "choice3": "Incinerates",
      "choice4": "Disintegrate",
      "answer": 3
    }
  ]
